David Von Drehle Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Lewis, Robert (Bobby), 1978-1982; Undated; nam_apap213-248 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Lockett v. Ohio, 1977; nam_apap213-249 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Lockhart v. Mcree, 1986; Undated; nam_apap213-250 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Long Gap, 1980-1984; Undated; nam_apap213-251 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Magee, Doug, 1980; Undated; nam_apap213-252 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Mail/feedback, 1988-1989; 1994; Undated; nam_apap213-253 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Manuscript -Among the Lowest of the Dead, Undated; nam_apap213-254 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Marky, Ray, ca. 1991; Undated; nam_apap213-255 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Martinez, Bob, 1988-1990; Undated; nam_apap213-256 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- McClesky v. Kemp, 1984-1986; 1991; Undated; nam_apap213-257 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- McCray, James (Doug), 1978; 1982-1983; 1991; Undated; nam_apap213-258 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- McRae - cases/moratorium [Judge], 1967-1972; Undated; nam_apap213-259 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- The Miami Herald, 1979; nam_apap213-260 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Nelson, Walter "Mad Dog", 1986; nam_apap213-261 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Nelson, Wendy - L.O.V.E., 1981-1982; 1984-1986; 1991-1992; Undated; nam_apap213-262 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- New York, 1986; 1989-1990; Undated; nam_apap213-263 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Op-ed - Anti, 1977-1981; 1984-1985; 1987-1990; 1992-1993; Undated; nam_apap213-264 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Op-ed - Pro, 1977; 1981; 1984-1985; 1988-1990; Undated; nam_apap213-265 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Operation Besmirchment - Graham, 1980; Undated; nam_apap213-266 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Override, 1975; 1980; 1984-1986; 1991-1992; Undated; nam_apap213-267 (Box 6, Folder 40-41)
- Palm Beach P.D., 1982-1983; Undated; nam_apap213-268 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Palmes, Tim - case accounts, 1984; nam_apap213-269 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Palmes, Tim - execution, 1984; nam_apap213-270 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Palmes, Tim - litigation/clemency, 1982; Undated; nam_apap213-271 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Pitts, Freddie Lee, 1994; Undated; nam_apap213-272 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Polls/public opinion, 1967; 1971; 1981-1986; 1989-1993; Undated; nam_apap213-273 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Pro - Death Penalty, 1989; Undated; nam_apap213-274 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Proffitt, Chuck, 1979-1980; 1984; Undated; nam_apap213-275 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Proffitt - reaction, 1976; Undated; nam_apap213-276 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Proffitt v. Florida, 1975-1976; Undated; nam_apap213-277 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Proportionality, 1979-1980; 1985-1986; nam_apap213-278 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Prosecutors, 1979; 1990; nam_apap213-279 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Race of victim - Florida, 1977-1978; 1981; 1991; Undated; nam_apap213-280 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Racial Justice Act, 1990-1992; Undated; nam_apap213-281 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Radelet, Mike [Researcher], 1982; 1988; 1990; Undated; nam_apap213-282 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Raulerson, James - case accounts, Undated; nam_apap213-283 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Raulerson, James - celebrations, 1985; Undated; nam_apap213-284 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Raulerson, James - execution, 1985; Undated; nam_apap213-285 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Raulerson, James - litigation/clemency, 1983; nam_apap213-286 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Raulerson, James - victim, 1980; 1985; Undated; nam_apap213-287 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Retardation, 1989; nam_apap213-288 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Robinson, Steve [Judge], 1984-1987; Undated; nam_apap213-289 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Sanity/mentally ill, 1980; 1984; 1986; 1990-1992; Undated; nam_apap213-290 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Schwarzschild, Henry, 1990; Undated; nam_apap213-291 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Senate Select Committee, ca. 1972; nam_apap213-292 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Series - notes, 1988; Undated; nam_apap213-293 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
- Sex - procreation, 1992; nam_apap213-294 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Shevin, Bob [Attorney], 1967; 1972; 1976-1978; Undated; nam_apap213-295 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Shriner, Carl, 1979; 1982; 1984; nam_apap213-296 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Smith, Jim, 1971; 1982; 1984; 1986; Undated; nam_apap213-297 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Snurkowski, Carolyn [Attorney], Undated; nam_apap213-298 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Songer, Carl, 1989; nam_apap213-299 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Sources, 1986-1988; Undated; nam_apap213-300 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Spalding, Larry [Attorney], 1979; 1985; 1988-1989; Undated; nam_apap213-301 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Spaziano, Joseph, 1993; nam_apap213-302 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Spenkelink - aftermath, 1979-1980; Undated; nam_apap213-303 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Spenkelink - anniversaries, 1980-1981; 1989; Undated; nam_apap213-304 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Spenkelink - bio, 1977; 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-305 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Spenkelink - block investigation, 1979-1981; Undated; nam_apap213-306 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Spenkelink - chronology, Undated; nam_apap213-307 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Spenkelink - commentary, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-308 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Spenkelink - context, 1979; nam_apap213-309 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Spenkelink - death watch, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-310 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Spenkelink - execution, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-311 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Spenkelink - family, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-312 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Spenkelink - Fifth Circuit Court, 1979-1980; Undated; nam_apap213-313 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Spenkelink - first warrant, 1977-1978; nam_apap213-314 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Spenkelink - Florida Supreme Court, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-315 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Spenkelink - general/character, 1976; 1978-1979; Undated; nam_apap213-316 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Spenkelink - interviews, 1978; Undated; nam_apap213-317 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Spenkelink - last days, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-318 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Spenkelink - legislature, 1979; nam_apap213-319 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Spenkelink - litigation/clemency, 1977-1979; Undated; nam_apap213-320 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Spenkelink - memorials/funeral, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-321 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Spenkelink - protests, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-322 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Spenkelink - public reaction, 1979; Undated; nam_apap213-323 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Spenkelink - selection, 1979; 1990; nam_apap213-324 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Spenkelink - TV coverage, 1979; 1982-1984; 1986; nam_apap213-325 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Spenkelink - Thanksgiving brawl, 1978-1979; nam_apap213-326 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Spenkelink - warrant signed, 1979; nam_apap213-327 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Spenkelink - Warren Folks, 1981; nam_apap213-328 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Stano, Gerald, 1982-1983; nam_apap213-329 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Starke - Florida, 1979-1980; 1984; 1989-1990; Undated; nam_apap213-330 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Steffens, Betty [Attorney], Undated; nam_apap213-331 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Straight, Ronald - execution, 1986; nam_apap213-332 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Strategies - anti, Undated; nam_apap213-333 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Streamlining, 1979; 1987; 1989; Undated; nam_apap213-334 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Strickland v. Washington, 1983-1984; nam_apap213-335 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Sullivan - anniversary, 1984; nam_apap213-336 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Sullivan - case accounts/bio, 1973; 1980; 1983; Undated; nam_apap213-337 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Sullivan - commentary, 1983; nam_apap213-338 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Sullivan - execution, 1983; Undated; nam_apap213-339 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Sullivan - legal defense fund, 1983; Undated; nam_apap213-340 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Sullivan - litigation/clemency, 1979-1980; 1983; Undated; nam_apap213-341 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Sullivan - memorials, 1983; Undated; nam_apap213-342 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Sullivan - Pope, 1983; nam_apap213-343 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Sullivan - protests, 1983; nam_apap213-344 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Sullivan - writings/interviews, 1976-1983; 1991; Undated; nam_apap213-345 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Tafero, Jessie, 1977; 1982; 1990; 1992; Undated; nam_apap213-346 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Testimony - Congressional records, 1988; Undated; nam_apap213-347 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Texas, 1980; 1982; 1986; 1988-1989; 1991; nam_apap213-348 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Thomas, Daniel - bio, 1986; 1988; Undated; nam_apap213-349 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Thomas, Daniel - execution, 1986; nam_apap213-350 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Thomas, Daniel - litigation/clemency, 1982; nam_apap213-351 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Thomas, Daniel - reaction, 1986; nam_apap213-352 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Tibbs, Delbert, 1978; 1982; Undated; nam_apap213-353 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Trop v. Dulles, 1957; nam_apap213-354 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Tucker, Ken [Attorney], Undated; nam_apap213-355 (Box 7, Folder 68)
- United States Supreme Court - cases, 1980; 1983-1988; 1990; Undated; nam_apap213-356 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- United States Supreme Court - justices, 1979; 1983; 1986-1989; 1990; 1994; nam_apap213-357 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Vandiver, Margaret [Researcher], 1984; 1990-1991; Undated; nam_apap213-358 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Vasil, George, 1977; 1979; nam_apap213-359 (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Victims - survivors/families, 1981; 1983; 1985-1987; 1990; Undated; nam_apap213-360 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Violence, 1993-1994; nam_apap213-361 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Volunteers, 1983; 1990; nam_apap213-362 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Volunteer Lawyers Resource Center, 1989; nam_apap213-363 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Von Drehle Notes from Harry Blackmun's Papers on Death Penalty Jurisprudence at the Library of Congress, Undated; nam_apap213-364 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Washington, David - execution, 1984; Undated; nam_apap213-365 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Washington, David - litigation/clemency, 1981; 1984; nam_apap213-366 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Washington, David - remorse/bio, 1984; Undated; nam_apap213-367 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Wax, Bill [Photographer], Undated; nam_apap213-368 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- White, Beauford - execution, 1987; nam_apap213-369 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- White, Beauford - litigation/clemency, 1978; 1984-1987; nam_apap213-370 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
- Whitney, Dennis, 1968; 1971-1972; -1977; nam_apap213-371 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Witt, Johnny Paul - case, Undated; nam_apap213-372 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Witt, Johnny Paul - execution, 1985; nam_apap213-373 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Witt v. Florida, 1980; Undated; nam_apap213-374 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Wives/girlfriends, 1986; Undated; nam_apap213-375 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Ziegler, Tommy, 1986; 1992; Undated; nam_apap213-376 (Box 8, Folder 13)